Change is worth fighting for
The Best of Enemies is a drama, history film directed by Robin Bissell.
Centers on the unlikely relationship between Ann Atwater, an
outspoken civil rights activist, and C.P.
Ellis, a local Ku Klux Klan leader who reluctantly co-chaired a community summit, battling over the
desegregation of schools in Durham, North Carolina during the racially-charged summer of 1971.
The incredible events that unfolded would change Durham
and the lives of Atwater and Ellis forever.
Ann Atwater, played by Taraji P. Henson.
Claiborne Paul Ellis, played by Sam Rockwell.
Bill Riddick, played by Babou Ceesay.
Mary Ellis, played by Anne Heche.
Floyd Kelly, played by Wes Bentley.
Garland Keith, played by Nick Searcy.
The Best of Enemies is a 2019 American drama film directed and
written by Robin Bissell in his feature debut.
It is based on the 1996 book The Best of Enemies: Race and Redemption in the New South by Osha Gray Davidson,
which focuses on the rivalry between civil rights activist Ann Atwater and Ku Klux Klan leader C.
The film stars Taraji P.
Henson, Sam Rockwell, Babou Ceesay, Anne Heche, Wes Bentley,
Bruce McGill, John Gallagher Jr., and Nick Searcy.
It was released in the United States on April 5, 2019, by STX Entertainment.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, ku klux
klan, 1970s, north carolina, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.